Niyasudheen PM **Front-End Developer**

in Niyasudheen PM

zydniyas

niyasthangal857@gmail.com

zydniyas.com 😵

Profile

I am a front-end developer skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and its frameworks With 2+ years of experience, I create visually appealing, responsive websites. I stay current with web development trends and apply strong logical problem-solving skills to optimize code and debug issues. I enjoy collaborating with designers and back-end developers to bring visions to life.

Skills

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, etc.

Frameworks and Library: React, Next.js Astro, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Sass, etc.

Basics on: C, Java, Python, Android development, SQL, PHP, DBMS, Shell Scripting, and Node.js.

Other Skills: Version Control/Git, Responsive Design, Basic Graphic Design Skills, Animation Skills (CSS/JavaScript),

SEO, etc.

Work Experience

Mojgenie IT Solutions

Junior Web Developer

Mojgenie IT Solutions

Frontend Developer

sep 2024 - Current

sep 2022 - 2024

Projects

Rental Website 2024 - Present

Developed the frontend for the Rental website, similar to boogable.com, using HTML, CSS, and React. Ensured a seamless user experience with mobile responsiveness and optimized performance.

• Role: Frontend Developer

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, React

Panda Cake E-commerce

Nov 2022 - Present

Developed the frontend of Panda Cake, an e-commerce platform dedicated to cakes, using a tech stack that includes HTML, CSS, SCSS, and JavaScript. The responsive design ensures a seamless and visually appealing online shopping experience for customers.

• Role: Frontend Developer

• Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript

Badge Creator Web Application

2024

Developed a badge-creating web application for the company's printing purposes using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. The application allows for customizable badge designs, improving the efficiency of internal printing processes.

• Role: Web Developer

• Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

KTX (Kerala Technology Expo 2024 Website)

Dec 2023 - Present

Developed KTX website using Astro framework and Tailwind CSS for a dynamic and responsive user experience.

• Role: Frontend Developer

• Tech Stack: Astro, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript

Live link: https://ktx.global/

GSoft Cloud Nov 2022 - Present

Led the development of GSoft Cloud, a 100+ page website. Created a unique design using custom classes, avoiding external CSS frameworks. Utilized Astro, SASS, and JavaScript for a seamless user experience.

• Role: Frontend Developer

• Tech Stack : Astro, SASS, JavaScript

Live link: https://www.gsoftcomm.net/

Explore more of my work in my portfolio https://zydniyas.github.io/portfolio/

Education

Bsc Computer Science

2019 - 2022

CAS Vattamkulam

Contact me

\(+91 8304985914

niyasthangal857@gmail.com 🔀